// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is NOT an ingredient of a Long Island Iced Tea?', 
      a: 'White Rum', 
      b: 'Dark Rum',
      c: 'Sour Mix',
      d: 'Gin',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What non-alchoholic drink is the Back Nine based on?', 
      a: 'Shirley Temple', 
      b: 'Limeade',
      c: 'Arnold Palmer',
      d: 'Roy Rogers',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What two spirits are combined and sold as "B&B"?', 
      a: 'Bourbon and Brandy', 
      b: 'Brandy and Benedictine',
      c: 'Benedictine and Bourbon',
      d: 'Brandy and Bitters',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What spirit was originally produced by letting apple cider freeze and removing the ice, thereby increasing the alcohol content?', 
      a: 'Applejack', 
      b: 'Apple Scnhapps',
      c: 'Apple Brandy',
      d: 'Sour Apple Four Loko',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is notoriously difficult about making a Ramos Gin Fizz?', 
      a: 'It requires dry ice', 
      b: 'It requires freshly-carbonated mineral water',
      c: 'It requires tempering eggs',
      d: 'It must be shaken for an extrodinarily long time',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'The Boulevardier cocktail contains bourbon, sweet vermouth and what else?', 
      a: 'Chartreuse', 
      b: 'Campari',
      c: 'Amaro',
      d: 'Luxardo',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'If you add sweet vermouth to a classic martini, what is the resulting drink called?', 
      a: 'A dirty martini', 
      b: 'A perfect martini',
      c: 'A muddy martini',
      d: 'A dumb martini',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of the canvas bag used to crush ice for drinks like the Mint Julep?', 
      a: 'Bully Bag', 
      b: 'Ice Bag',
      c: 'Lewis Bag',
      d: 'Barbacks Bagster',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What kind of drink is made with the rhyming ratios "one of sour, two of sweet, three of strong and four of weak"?', 
      a: 'rickey', 
      b: 'smash',
      c: 'punch',
      d: 'cooler',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What drink is made with just gin (or vodka), simple syrup, and lime juice?', 
      a: 'A daquiri', 
      b: 'A gimlet',
      c: 'A Tom Collins',
      d: 'A Phil Collins',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};